Guide to the Central Washington University Relations, Subject Files 1960-2005 (bulk 1980-2000)
Central Washington University Archives and Special Collections
- Sociology Department – Newspaper Clippings (Box-folder 26-8)
- Sports – News Releases (Box-folder 26-9)
- Sports – Newspaper Clippings (Box-folder 26-10)
- Staff Personnel (Box-folder 26-11)
- State Auditor’s Report (Box-folder 26-12)
- Strategic Plan (Box-folder 26-13)
- Student Activities (Box-folder 26-14)
- Student Affairs – General File (Box-folder 26-15)
- Student Affairs – General File (Box-folder 27-1)
- Student Affairs – News Releases and Clippings (Box-folder 27-2)
- Student Demands, 1969 (Box-folder 27-3)
- Student Empowerment (Box-folder 27-4)
- Student Fees (Box-folder 27-5)
- Student Health and Counseling Center – General File (Box-folder 27-6)
- Student Health and Counseling Center – News Releases and Clippings (Box-folder 27-7)
- Students – Miscellaneous (Box-folder 27-8)
- Substitute Senate Bill #5688 – Commercial Activities (Box-folder 27-9)
- Summer Session (Box-folder 27-10)
- Taco Bell (Box-folder 27-11)
- Tang Ranch (Box-folder 27-12)
- Teacher Education Program – News Releases (Box-folder 28-1)
- Teacher Education Program – Newspaper Clippings (Box-folder 28-2)
- Teaching English as a Second Language (Box-folder 28-3)
- Teaching Program – Early Childhood Education (Box-folder 28-4)
- Teaching Program – Elementary Education (Box-folder 28-5)
- Teaching Program – Health Education (Box-folder 28-6)
- Teaching Program – Special Education (Box-folder 28-7)
- Telecommunications Project (Box-folder 28-8)
- Television, Video Cable Channel 10 (Box-folder 28-9)
- Theatre Arts Department – General File (Box-folder 28-10)
- Theatre Arts Department – News Releases (Box-folder 28-11)
- Theatre Arts Department – News Releases (Box-folder 28-12)
- Theatre Arts Department – Newspaper Clippings (Box-folder 28-13)
- Thitymile Fire (Box-folder 28-14)
- Totem Pole (Brooks Library) (Box-folder 28-15)
- Trustees – General File (Box-folder 29-1)
- Trustees – List of Members (Box-folder 29-2)
- Trustees – Members (Box-folder 29-3)
- Trustees – Members, Gwen B. Chaplin (Box-folder 29-4)
- Trustees – Members, Leslie D. Jones (Box-folder 29-5)
- Trustees – Members, Kenneth Martin (Box-folder 29-6)
- Trustees – Members, Jay A. Reich (Box-folder 29-7)
- Trustees – Members, Nadine Romero (Box-folder 29-8)
- Trustees – Members, Mike Sells (Box-folder 29-9)
- Trustees – Members, Judy Yu (Box-folder 29-10)
- Trustees – Members, Group Photographs (Box-folder 29-11)
- Trustees – News Releases (Box-folder 29-12)
- Trustees – News Releases (Box-folder 29-13)
- Trustees – Newspaper Clippings (Box-folder 29-14)
- Trustees – Newspaper Clippings (Box-folder 29-15)
- Tuition and Fees – General File (Box-folder 29-16)
- Tuition and Fees – General File (Box-folder 29-17)
- Tuition and Fees – News Releases and Clippings (Box-folder 30-1)
- Visions, Missions and Goals (Box-folder 30-2)
- United Faculty of CWU (Box-folder 30-3)
- University Bookstore (Box-folder 30-4)
- United Daycare and Preschool (Box-folder 30-5)
- University English as a Second Language (Box-folder 30-6)
- University Logo (Box-folder 30-7)
- University Relations and Development – General Files (Box-folder 30-8)
- University Relations and Development – News Releases (Box-folder 30-9)
- University Relations and Development – Newspaper Clippings (Box-folder 30-10)
- Veterans Affairs (Box-folder 30-11)
- WHETS Distance Learning (Box-folder 30-12)
- Washington Federation of State Employees (Box-folder 30-13)
- Water Lab (Box-folder 30-14)
- Women’s Resource Center (Box-folder 30-15)
- Women’s Studies (Box-folder 30-16)
- Workplace Safety Institute (Box-folder 30-17)
- YK2 (Box-folder 30-18)
- Conferences and Workshops – Newspaper Clippings (Box-folder 31-1)
- Conferences and Workshops – Newspaper Clippings (Box-folder 31-2)
- English Department – News Releases (Box-folder 31-3)
- English Department – News Releases (Box-folder 31-4)
- English Department – Newspaper Clippings (Box-folder 31-5)
- Higher Education Coordinating Board – Newspaper Clippings (Box-folder 31-6)
- Higher Education Coordinating Board – Newspaper Clippings (Box-folder 31-7)
- History Department – News Releases (Box-folder 31-8)
- History Department – Newspaper Clippings (Box-folder 31-9)
- International Studies – News Releases (Box-folder 31-10)
- International Studies – Newspaper Clippings (Box-folder 31-11)
- Art Department – Newspaper Clippings, 1945-1950 (Box-folder 32-1)
- Art Department – Newspaper Clippings, 1951-1954 (Box-folder 32-2)
- Art Department – Newspaper Clippings, 1955-1963 (Box-folder 32-3)
- Art Department – Newspaper Clippings – Photocopies (Box-folder 32-4)
- Athletics Department – Newspaper Clippings, 1941-1966 (Box-folder 32-5)
- Athletics Department – Newspaper Clippings - Photocopies (Box-folder 32-6)
- Book Store – Newspaper Clippings, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 32-7)
- Extension and Evening Classes – Newspaper Clippings, 1947-1959 (Box-folder 32-8)
- Extension and Evening Classes – Newspaper Clippings – Photocopies (Box-folder 32-9)
- Music – Concerts, shows, etc. – Newspaper Clippings, 1945-1948 (Box-folder 32-10)
- Music – Concerts, shows, etc. – Newspaper Clippings, 1949-1951 (Box-folder 32-11)
- Music – Concerts, shows, etc. – Newspaper Clippings, 1952-1957 (Box-folder 32-12)
- Music – Concerts, shows, etc. – Newspaper Clippings – Photocopies (Box-folder 32-13)
- Music Department – Newspaper Clippings, 1954-1965 (Box-folder 32-14)
- Music Department – Newspaper Clippings – Photocopies (Box-folder 32-15)
- Registrar’s Office – Commencement – Newspaper Clippings, 1932-1985 (Box-folder 32-16)
- Registrar’s Office – Commencement – Newspaper Clippings – Photocopies (Box-folder 32-17)
- Registrar’s Office – Enrollment – Newspaper Clippings, 1946-1964 (Box-folder 32-18)
- Registrar’s Office – Enrollment – Newspaper Clippings – Photocopies (Box-folder 32-19)
- ROTC – Air Force – Newsletters and Newspaper Clippings, 1960-1963 (Box-folder 32-20)
- ROTC – Air Force – Newsletters and Newspaper Clippings – Photocopies (Box-folder 32-21)
- ROTC – Military History – Newspaper Clippings, 1953-1958 (Box-folder 32-22)
- ROTC – Military History – Newspaper Clippings – Photocopies (Box-folder 32-23)
- Scholarships – Newspaper Clippings, 1986-1992 (Box-folder 33-1)
- Scholarships – Press Releases, 1986-1989 (Box-folder 33-2)
- Scholarships – Press Releases, 1990-1992 (Box-folder 33-3)
- Student Deaths – Lisa Brockett, 1987 (Box-folder 33-4)
- Student Deaths – Susan Rancourt, 1989 (Box-folder 33-5)
- Students – Miscellaneous – Newspaper Clippings, 1991 (Box-folder 33-6)
- Students – Miscellaneous – Newspaper Clippings, 1992 (Box-folder 33-7)
- Tuition and Fees – Newspaper Clippings, 1986-1991 (Box-folder 33-8)
- Urban Center, Teacher Education Programs – Newspaper Clippings, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 33-9)
- Washington State Conference for Women, 1977 (Box-folder 33-10)
- Women’s Resource Center and Women’s Studies Program – Newspaper Clippings, 1978-1991 (Box-folder 33-11)
- Yearbook Feasibility Study, 1979 (Box-folder 33-12)
- Music / Bands – Newspaper Clippings, 1973-1991 (Box-folder 34-1)
- Music / Bands – Press Releases, 1975-1991 (Box-folder 34-2)
- Music / Choral – Newspaper Clippings, 1984-1991 (Box-folder 34-3)
- Music / Choral – Press Releases, 1986-1990 (Box-folder 34-4)
- Music / Faculty and Guest Recitals – Newspaper Clippings, 1977-1991 (Box-folder 34-5)
- Music / Faculty and Guest Recitals – Press Releases, 1988-1991 (Box-folder 34-6)
- Music / Faculty and Guest Recitals – Press Releases, 1979-1987 (Box-folder 34-7)
- Music / Jazz – Newspaper Clippings, 1974-1991 (Box-folder 34-8)
- Music / Jazz – Press Releases, 1986-1991 (Box-folder 34-9)
- Music / Orchestra – Press Releases, 1975-1991 (Box-folder 34-10)
- Music / Student and Group Recitals, 1971-1991 (Box-folder 34-11)
- Music Department – Newspaper Clippings, 1986-1990 (Box-folder 34-12)
- Music Department – Press Releases (Box-folder 34-13)
- “The Runner Stumbles" – Filming at CWU, 1978 (Box-folder 34-14)
- Sarah Spurgeon Gallery – Newspaper Clippings, 1989-1992 (Box-folder 34-15)
- Sarah Spurgeon Gallery – Press Releases (Box-folder 34-16)
- Scholarships – Newspaper Clippings, 1986-1992 (Box-folder 34-17)